<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<rss version="2.0">

<!-- My manually updated RSS feed -->

<channel>

    <title>Brendon J. Brewer's website and blog</title>
    <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/</link>
    <description>Bayesian statistics and other things of interest to
                 Brendon J. Brewer</description>


   <item>
        <guid>#cricket-feedback</guid>
        <title>Some nice feedback on our latest cricket paper</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#cricket-feedback</link>
        <description>This afternoon I had my weekly meeting with PhD student
                Ollie
                Stevenson. It was a routine meeting where he showed me
                what he'd been working on and we discussed a few issues
                around it. Then he mentioned that our most recently submitted
                paper had received some feedback. It was pretty good feedback!
                Check this out: [IMAGE]

                Thanks, Nick! This was super pleasing to read.
                I just hope the journal referees feel the same way, or at least
                half as positively. But until
                we hear back from them you can get the preprint
                from the arxiv
                or (why not) from LBRY.</description>
    </item>


   <item>
        <guid>#lookup-tables</guid>
        <title>Rocking Lookup Tables in 2019</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#lookup-tables</link>
        <description>Do people learn about lookup tables anymore? I don't know where
                I picked them up from, but I have the impression that they are
                an old-fashioned programming technique from the 1980s and 1990s.
                However, I find myself using them all the time even though it's 2019.</description>
    </item>


   <item>
        <guid>#hygiene-theatre</guid>
        <title>Hygiene Theatre?</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#hygiene-theatre</link>
        <description>This morning I bought a muffin from the convenience store on
                campus. In front of the muffins there is a sign instructing us
                to use the tongs to pick up a muffin, instead of our possibly
                grotty hands...</description>
    </item>

   <item>
        <guid>#two-songs</guid>
        <title>Two singers and songs I've been enjoying</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#two-songs</link>
        <description>On my old blog I occasionally posted songs that I'm into, for
                no particular reason other than wanting to share them...</description>
    </item>


   <item>
        <guid>#worth-doing-once</guid>
        <title>Something worth doing once</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#worth-doing-once</link>
        <description>Attentive readers and/or stalkers may have noticed a recent
                addition on the research page of this site: a paper accepted
                for publication in Nature. This was an interesting collaboration
                with my PhD supervisor Geraint Lewis, whom I visited last year...</description>
    </item>



   <item>
        <guid>#busy-again</guid>
        <title>Busy again...</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#busy-again</link>
        <description>It's been pretty quiet here since I've been busy again. Here
                are the two main reasons:</description>
    </item>



   <item>
        <guid>#recently-discovered-tools</guid>
        <title>Recently discovered tools</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#recently-discovered-tools</link>
        <description>In the last couple of months I've come across some pretty
                cool new programs that I thought I'd tell you all about
                (I know I have at least one reader: I got a really
                nice email from a former student who reads the blog)...</description>
    </item>


    <item>
        <guid>#book-quotes</guid>
        <title>Some quotes used in my book draft</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#book-quotes</link>
        <description>I sometimes tell my graduate students that the most important
                section of their dissertation is the acknowledgements. This
                is because it will be
                read by far more people than the rest, by a wide margin.
                After the acknowledgements, the next most important part
                is to put in some interesting or fun quotes at the beginning
                of the chapters...</description>
    </item>



    <item>
        <guid>#a-new-experience</guid>
        <title>A new experience</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#a-new-experience</link>
        <description>A month or two ago, Lianne and I bought a Yamaha MT-03 to help with commuting. It's
                been really fun riding again, though of course I have plenty
                of reasons for caution on the roads. Today I experienced a
                hazard I've never encountered before...</description>
    </item>



    <item>
        <guid>#lbry-support</guid>
        <title>How to support a file or channel on LBRY without spending anything</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#lbry-support</link>
        <description>As my loyal reader knows, I've been into LBRY for a while now after hearing
                about it from economist Alex Tabarrok. It still has a ways to go to be fully featured
                and get more adoption, but it's been a fun thing to learn about
                and play with. Today I wanted to tell you about a cool feature that isn't supported
                in the GUI app yet but can be done from the command line...</description>
    </item>




    <item>
        <guid>#busy-busy-busy</guid>
        <title>Busy busy busy</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#busy-busy-busy</link>
        <description>The initial flurry of posts here may have implied that I would
                be keeping up that rate long term. I can't promise that, but I
                will try to post regularly still. Things have been pretty busy
                with teaching STATS 731 for the first time...</description>
    </item>



    <item>
        <guid>#eighties-australiana</guid>
        <title>80s Australiana/Nostalgia</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#eighties-australiana</link>
        <description>When I lived in Australia, I never really paid much
            attention to the popular pop/rock singers that Australia had
            produced. I think I thought of them (Jimmy Barnes, John Farnham
            et al) as cheesy...</description>
    </item>


    <item>
        <guid>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#pewdiepie-lbry</guid>
        <title>How many PewDiePies are there on LBRY?</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#pewdiepie-lbry</link>
        <description>Answer: 36. That's 36 people who don't understand the LBRY
                naming/URL system, which works using a form of auction that
                provides no incentive to squatting...</description>
    </item>


    <item>
        <guid>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#singing-project</guid>
        <title>Singing in other people's backyards</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#singing-project</link>
        <description>A quote from statistician John Tukey that is a cliché for a
                reason
                is "the best thing about being a statistician is that you get
                to
                play in everyone's backyard". Sometimes, other people invite
                you
                to their backyards,
                like
                geophysicist Mike Rowe did. Other times, you just invite
                yourself
                over...</description>
    </item>


    <item>
        <guid>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#using-220-skills</guid>
        <title>Using STATS 220 skills in the wild</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#using-220-skills</link>
        <description>One of the best and worst things about being an academic is
                that sometimes you are assigned to teach a course about
                something you aren't very good at, or in some cases, have
                never learned at all. As long as you can keep ahead of the
                students, it usually works out fine. I've been lucky so far
                that this hasn't happened much, and when it has, I've been
                grateful to have learned the new material...</description>
    </item>


    <item>
        <guid>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#maxent-and-homogeneity</guid>
        <title>MaxEnt and homogeneity</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#maxent-and-homogeneity</link>
        <description>I'm a bit unusual among Bayesians in that I still think the principle of maximum entropy
                is both true and (occasionally) useful, and that its critics have thrown out the
                baby with the bathwater. One of the chapters of my upcoming book,
                if I finish it, will be about this issue, and related ones such as where
                MaxEnt constraints come from in the first place...</description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <guid>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#lovely-email-received</guid>
        <title>Lovely email received!</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#lovely-email-received</link>
        <description>This kind of thing makes my day...</description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <guid>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#conventions-wide-priors</guid>
        <title>Conventions for wide priors in JAGS/BUGS</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#conventions-wide-priors</link>
        <description>I'm currently preparing to teach STATS 731, the graduate
                Bayesian course here.
                My first lecture was meant to be today but
                I had to cancel it due to hoarseness following a throat
                infection. Anyway, the existing course materials use a lot
                of the traditional (in statistics) wide priors, stuff like this
                for a location and scale parameter respectively...</description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <guid>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#talk-dallas-willard</guid>
        <title>Talk by Dallas Willard about worldviews</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#talk-dallas-willard</link>
        <description>I recently enjoyed
                this excellent talk
                by Dallas Willard, entitled The Nature and
                Necessity of Worldviews. If you're familiar with
                Jonathan Haidt's work, it strikes familiar notes,
                but Willard's personal angle as a frustrated
                Christian in the secular university comes through...</description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <guid>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#trying-maths-here</guid>
        <title>Trying out maths here</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#trying-maths-here</link>
        <description>When I moved my blog over here, I was a bit worried that I
                wouldn't be able
                to type \(\LaTeX\) anymore. But that's not the case!...</description>
    </item>

    <item>
        <guid>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#retiring-blog</guid>
        <title>Retiring the Plausibility Theory blog</title>
        <link>https://www.brendonbrewer.com/blog.html#retiring-blog</link>
        <description>The other day I bought a domain name for my website, which
                was fun, and has motivated me to continue simplifying
                my internet
                life in a few ways. Over the last year or so I've successfully
                reduced my social media usage by about 80%, and am now using
                the internet like it's 1999 again...</description>
    </item>
</channel>

</rss>
